Nicholas Finn

Mobile: (303) 253-5954 Email: <u>nick.finn6@gmail.com</u>

Goal oriented performer who exemplifies self-motivation, efficiency, and reliability. Strengths in organization, problem-solving, and resourcefulness, with over 10 years experience of successful customer service. Proven to work well under pressure with minimal support or supervision.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Target —Produce Clerk

Nov 2020 - Current

Efficiently unloads, organizes, and displays product shipments. Works to maintain daily presentation of product while aiding customers on the floor.

- In addition to efficiently completing tasks for produce, provides frequent support to multiple departments with overflow
- Consistently meets task deadlines
- Recognized by supervisors to be versatile and flexible

Kroger — Cashier, Self-Check-out Attendant

March 2018 - June 2020

Handled cash, credit, and check transactions, resolved payment problems, greeted customers and helped with store navigation when needed.

- In the moment problem-solving to meet customer satisfaction
- Supervised 6 self-check-out kiosks at once

King Soopers — Cashier, Fuel Clerk, Customer Service

Feb 2016 - Feb 2018

Solo-managed separate fuel center while performing upkeep tasks and customer service.

- Maintained a 12-pump site with limited support and supervision
- Provided in-store back-up as needed

Albertsons — Produce clerk, Fresh Cut Clerk

Sept 2011 - Nov 2015

Responsible for documenting inventory, handling food, product presentation, and maintaining a clean and organized environment.

Notable efficiency as productivity directly influenced product sales

EDUCATION

Pursuing a degree in computer science

Dallas College, Dallas (Currently enrolled)

University of Colorado at Colorado Springs, Colorado Springs (Aug 2013 – May 2015)

Relevant Coursework

Intro to Computer Science, Focus Language: Java, Programming Fundamentals 1, Focus Language C++

Software Proficiencies

Microsoft Office, Zoom

References

Glenn Hennig Target, Team Leader (214)-264-6174 Calvin Bosch Target, Assistant Store Manager (469)-258-0451